3rd day living in 1 Chevette with R$1 in his pocket.
Today I will invest in my business
and around the time I was consulting on the internet.
There's a nine and ninety bid,
the plan is month nine and ninety.
This one.
He has no legitimacy when we register,
he signed the contract at nine and ninety.
Ah,
the time and I can start today.
Agorinha talks to CPF music.
09:90 uncle,
let's see if it worked out well.
Before receiving a visit,
tidy up your home.
Every place there is a cultural code.
First I need to see what people like to do.
If we know a little more about the city's culture,
it ends up being easier for us to get it right than we are going to do.
Bora know then
Is everything okay?
I think I had an idea,
bro.
Taking the picture there?
I've done it on Canva here now
Don't touch me,
I'm a Real Life Wire.